imgstg.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy | SportsTG

**Last Updated 12 September 2019**

**Introduction**

Welcome to Stack Sports, a Web-based software toolset for athletes, parents, coaches, team managers and tournament directors, operated by SPay, Inc. d/b/a Stack Sports (“Stack Sports,” “we,” “our,” or “us”). Stack Sports owns and operates the following websites, applications, services and tools (collectively, our “Service” or “Services”):  

**Association Connect**

**CaptainU**

**Club & League Connect**

**CrazyRaise**

**FSP (SportsTG)**

**Game Officials (SportsTG)**

**Gameday (SportsTG)**

**GamePlan**

**Goalline**

**GroupNet Solutions**

**Ignite**

**League Lineup**

**National Data Center (USAF)**

**National Data Center (USSF)**

**OST/Classic (SportsTG)**

**Pointstreak**

**Racewire**

**Regatta Central**

**SDI Camps**

**SportsTG**

**Stack**

**Stack Pay**

**Team Connect**

**Tournament Connect**

Stack Sports is committed to protecting your privacy and to treating your personal information as you would want it to be treated. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose and protect your personal information.

**Stack Sports as a Data Controller and Data Processor**

The scope of Stack Sports’ responsibilities for protection of personal data depend on whether we are acting as a “data controller” or a “data processor” with respect to a particular set of processing operations. Data controllers determine what personal data is collected, the purpose of that data collection, and the means, while data processors assist them to complete these tasks efficiently. Under the laws of many countries, and especially in the EU with the entry into force of the GDPR, data controllers bear primary responsibility for compliance with data protection laws and for respecting the privacy rights of individuals. 

In providing the Services, Stack Sports acts variously as a data controller, a data processor, or both. 

Some of our Services are intended for use by organizations such as national governing bodies, sports clubs, and teams (“Institutional User(s)”). For those Services, it is the Institutional User which, as the data controller, collects and determines the purpose(s) for processing of personal data of athletes, coaches, fans, or other individuals (“End Users”). Stack Sports’ role as data processor is to provide Institutional User(s) with the functionalities of the particular Service utilizing the personal data made available or shared by the Institutional User. 

Every Institutional User will process and store personal information in different ways, and this Privacy Policy cannot and is not intended to cover each of them. End Users with questions or wishing to exercise their privacy rights with respect to personal data processed by Stack Sports on behalf of Institutional Users should review the privacy policies Institutional Users have prepared and address inquiries to them. Nevertheless, in order to provide End Users with supplementary information and transparency, this Privacy Policy describes in general terms our data processing practices across all of our Services, regardless of whether or not we act as data controller. 

Stack Sports also makes some of its Services available directly to individual athletes, parents, coaches, and team managers (“Direct Users”). For example, Direct Users may create personal accounts with one or more of our Services which require them to disclose personal information in order to function properly. Finally, Stack Sports may utilize personal data provided by Institutional Users for purposes other than those determined by the Institutional Users. In these contexts, Stack Sports acts as a data controller and the terms of this Privacy Policy, including with respect to the exercise of data privacy rights, are fully applicable. 

**What information does Stack Sports collect?**

We collect or are provided access to a variety of personal information about our End Users and Direct Users so that we can provide our Services. Personal information means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identifying information has been removed (anonymous data).

We do our best to be as transparent as possible about our data practices and how we may collect, use, store, and transfer your personal information. 

The categories of information we collect can include:

  * **Identity information** – Collected for registration and profile information when Direct Users join a Service, or provided by Institutional Users. Identity information may include username, first and last name, birthdate, phone number, email address, and other contact information required to register for a Stack Sports account, participate in a Stack Sports promotion or contest, or to correspond with us.
  * **Financial information** – We may collect billing information to provide our premium Services, or process billing information on behalf of our Institutional Users.
  * **Profile information** – Data collected through the use of the Service. For Direct Users, after you set up your account, you may be able to provide additional information which may be shared through your profile, such as your height, weight, photograph and/or video and other biographical or personal information (“Profile Information”), and information about your athletic performance or information relating to your team, league, or organization. 

This information may be provided by a third party, such as a parent, association administrator, league administrator, team administrator, coach, tournament director (subject to your consent), or it may be provided by you directly (collectively, “Persons with Authority”). Persons with Authority may provide information about the club, league or team you play on as well as biographical, contact information, notes and commentary related to your activities. We also collect information about how you use our Service and the data you input.

  * **Contact Information –** Stack Sports may collect information from an address book or stored contact list that a Direct User uploads or otherwise provides access to Stack Sports.
  * **Information from third parties –** Stack Sports may collect information about Direct Users and End Users from publicly available sources or other third parties, including Institutional Users, such as your tournament schedule, team name, ranking, player statistics, etc. Stack Sports may also receive information about you when you interact with our sites through various social media, for example, by liking us on Facebook, following us on Twitter, or connecting on Instagram, Vimeo, or other social networks. The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the social network. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Stack Sports Service.
  * **User activity –** Stack Sports may at our discretion, but are not obligated to, monitor the communications that take place on our Service, such as messaging, in order to protect our Direct Users and monitor the effectiveness of our Service. You acknowledge that you have no expectation of privacy with respect to any such communications or postings, and you expressly consent to such monitoring.
  * **Online tracking information** – Stack Sports automatically collects certain types of usage information when you visit our website or use our Service. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites. Please see our cookie policy below for further details.

**How does Stack Sports use your personal information?**

We use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features of the Service, including to communicate with you. The use of your personal information is fully in accordance with:

  1. The contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you;
  2. Our necessary and legitimate Interests (or those of a third party) in the provision of the Service, provided that your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests;
  3. Our effort to comply with applicable laws and regulations. 

Please **Contact Us** at [privacy@sportstg.com](mailto:privacy@sportstg.com) to find out more about the types of lawful basis that we will rely on to process your personal data.

**What are the purposes for Stack Sports’ applications use of your personal information?**

Service and intended user| Purpose/Activity| Personal Information| Lawful Basis for Processing  
---|---|---|---  
FSP (SportsTG)  
(Institutional User)| Club and league membership registration tools;  
Event management;  
Communication tools;  
Ecommerce tools;  
Invoicing and payment; Marketing to End Users  
| • Identity information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Profile information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Contact information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Payment information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Health information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
| Varies for each Institutional User. 

Personal Information is only shared with third parties subject to End Users’ affirmative consent.  
  
Game Officials (SportsTG)  
(Institutional User)  
| Club and league membership registration tools;  
Event management;  
Communication tools;  
Ecommerce tools;  
Invoicing and payment; Marketing to End Users  
| • Identity information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Contact information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Profile information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Payment information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
| Varies for each Institutional User. 

Personal Information is only shared with third parties subject to End Users’ affirmative consent.  
  
Gameday (SportsTG)  
(Institutional User)  
| Club and league membership registration tools;  
Event management;  
Communication tools;  
Ecommerce tools;  
Invoicing and payment; Marketing to End Users  
| • Identity information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Contact information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Profile information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Payment information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
| Varies for each Institutional User. 

Personal Information is only shared with third parties subject to End Users’ affirmative consent.  
  
GamePlan  
(Institutional User)  
| Tools to store, index, and organize video footage from athletic events for distribution to End Users.  
Marketing to End Users  
| • Identity information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Contact information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
| Varies for each Institutional User.

Personal Information is only shared with third parties subject to End Users’ affirmative consent.  
  
OST/Classic (SportsTG)  
(Institutional User)  
| Club and league membership registration tools;  
Event management;  
Communication tools;  
Ecommerce tools;  
Invoicing and payment; Marketing to End Users  
| • Identity information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Contact information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Profile information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Payment information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
| Varies for each Institutional User. 

Personal Information is only shared with third parties subject to End Users’ affirmative consent.  
  
Sports TG  
(Institutional User)  
| Club and league membership registration tools;  
Event management;  
Communication tools;  
Ecommerce tools;  
Invoicing and payment; Marketing to End Users  
| • Identity information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Contact information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Profile information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
• Payment information (Stack or DP User Acknowledged)  
| Varies for each Institutional User. 

Personal Information is only shared with third parties subject to End Users’ affirmative consent.  
  
**Does Stack Sports share and disclose information to third parties?**

We may share your personal information in the instances described below. For further information on your choices regarding your information, see the “Your Privacy Rights” section below.

Remember, some of our Services allows Direct Users to connect with others and share information about themselves with other individuals and organizations. In some instances, your Profile Information, including your name, photo, and other personal information, will be available publicly to other members of the Service by default and may be searchable by search engines which may display a certain amount of your information publicly. You may be able to adjust your profile settings to entirely prevent the general public from viewing your profile, though it will remain visible to other Direct Users of the Service. Also, remember that Institutional Users and other third parties that use Stack Sports Services may have their own data collection and use policies that Stack Sports does not control, even in situations where Stack Sports acts as a data processor on their behalf. Please review the privacy policies of any third-party organization before sharing your personal information with that organization.

We may also share Personal Information of End Users provided by Institutional Users for marketing purposes, subject to the End Users’ affirmative consent. As described above, in such cases Stack Sports acts as a data controller and End Users may contact us directly in order to exercise their privacy rights. 

We may share your personal information with:

  * Other companies owned by or under common ownership at Stack Sports. These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we can under this policy;
  * Third-party vendors and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, as needed to carry out their work for us, which may include identifying and serving targeted advertisements, billing, payment processing, content or service fulfillment, or providing analytic services;
  * Trusted business partners who may use your information to contact you about opportunities that may be of interest to you (subject to your affirmative consent).
  * Other Direct Users of the Stack Sports Service. Your information, including both information you provide and information we have collected about you from other Direct and/or Institutional Users, may be searchable by or made available to other Direct and/or Institutional Users of the Service. These users may contact you via email or via text messages (subject to your affirmative consent).
  * To Persons with Authority. Certain Stack Sports Services connect to colleges and universities. As such, Stack Sports may disclose your personal information directly or via a third party to colleges and universities that you have indicated you are interested in attending, as well as to other accredited colleges and universities that Stack Sports and/or our business partners believe may be of interest to you (subject to your affirmative consent).
  * Certain Stack Sports Services connect to the public. Any information that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service is viewable by other Users and the public. As one example, a tournament director may print a list of athletes at an event and distribute that list to tournament attendees who may or may not be members of the Service.
  * Other parties in connection with a company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of a bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings; and
  * Third parties as required by law or subpoena or otherwise if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use http://stacksports.com/termsofuse or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Stack Sports, our Users, or others.
  * We may also aggregate or otherwise strip data of all personally identifying characteristics and may share that aggregated, anonymized data with third parties.

If Stack Sports receives your Personal Information in the European Union and subsequently transfers that information to a third party agent or service provider for processing, Stack Sports remains responsible for ensuring that such third party agent or service provider processes your Personal Information to the standard required by our Model Contract Clause commitments (see the sections below headed “Additional Information for Users in the European Economic Area (“EEA”)” and “International Data Transfers”).

**Data Retention**

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide our Direct and Institutional Users with the Services; to maintain a record of your transactions for financial reporting, audit, and compliance purposes; and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce agreements, and as otherwise permitted by applicable law. Upon your request, Stack Sports, when acting as Data Controller, will deactivate your account or delete your Personal Information.

**Your Privacy Rights**

**What choices do I have?**

If you are a Direct User, you can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of most of the features of our Services. 

**Cookies**

Like many companies, Stack Sports uses cookies and other common tracking technologies to help us better understand your use and needs of our Services, guide development of future products, and learn how we can improve. For example:

  * based on your cookie settings, we may track information indicating, among other things, which pages of the website were visited, the order in which they were visited, when they were visited, and which hyperlinks and other user interface controls were used;
  * We may log the IP address, operating system, and browser software you used when accessing the Service, and we may be able to determine from an IP address your Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of your point of connectivity; and
  * We may track and collect information from emails that we send to you, for example whether you opened the email or clicked on any links from the email.

Stack Sports also partners with third parties to help us track and understand your activity on our Services, how you interact with our social media, and how you find or may be referred to our Services.

Stack Sports uses cookies and other tracking technologies for the following purposes:

  * when necessary for system administration, security, and integrity to ensure the Services work properly for you. Without these technologies, the Service may not function correctly; and
  * to enable analytics, performance and functionality, to help us gather information about how visitors use the Service, monitor the Service’s performance, and to enhance your experience by recognizing and remembering whether you have used the Service before and may have any personal preferences.

**Marketing Communications**

You can opt-out of receiving certain promotional or marketing communications from us at any time, by using the unsubscribe link in the emails communications we send.

If you have any account for our Services, we will still send you non-promotional communications, like service related emails.

**How Can I Exercise My Data Subject Rights?**

If you would like to access, review, update, rectify, or delete any Personal Information we hold about you, or exercise any other data subject right available to you under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), please contact our privacy team at privacy@sportstg.com. Our privacy team will examine your request and respond to you as quickly as possible.

Please note that we may still use any aggregated and de-identified Personal Information that does not identify any individual, and may also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**International Data Transfers**

Personal Information you submit on the Websites or through the Services is sent to the Australia and will be primarily processed by us in the Australia and potentially in other countries, on our servers or on our hosted service providers’ cloud servers on our behalf.  We will always protect your information, as agreed upon with Processing Model Contract Clauses executed with each respective Data Processor and/or Data Controller,  in accordance with this Privacy Policy wherever it is processed.

**International Data Transfers – Additional information for users in the European Economic Area (“EEA”)**

**Stack Sports is self-certified to the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework**

This section sets out the privacy principles we follow with respect to transfers of Personal Information from the EEA to Australia, including Personal Information we receive from individuals residing in the EEA who visit our Websites and/or who may use of our Services or otherwise interact with us.

Please note that for users located in the EEA, the term Personal Information used in this Policy is equivalent to the term “personal data” under applicable European data protection laws.

Stack Sports complies with the EU GDPR through respective Data Processing Model Contract Clauses executed with each respective Data Controller and Data Processor U.S. regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information from European Union member countries. These Model Clauses follow such Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. 

We commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information.  SportsTG website visitors located within the EEA with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact us at [privacy@sportstg.com](mailto:privacy@sportstg.com).  

SportsTG application users, such as those utilizing our OST, Classic, FSP Software as a Service, should contact [privacy@sportstg.com](mailto:privacy@sportstg.com) to:

  * Acknowledge or Decline specific terms of use disclosed in each respective privacy policy and any updates thereof;
    * Request to be unsubscribed from marketing email notifications;
    * Request to be forgotten – erasure;
  * Request to learn what personal information is being collected, used, and retained
  * Request to receive all personal information is being collected, used, and retained

We commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information.  Application users with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact us at [privacy@sportstg.com](mailto:privacy@sportstg.com).  

Please note that Stack Sports is required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

**Children**

Unless explicitly stated otherwise when Direct Users create an account with one of our Services, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. Our Services which do collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 comply with GDPR, meaning that: 

  * we will provide parents with direct notice of our information practices and obtain their verifiable consent before collecting their children’s Personal Information; and 
  * we will respect parents’ right to delete or restrict Stack Sports’ use of that Personal Information. 

**Linked Websites**

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We’re constantly trying to improve our Websites and Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well. We will alert you to material changes by, for example, placing a notice on our Websites and/or by sending you a notification as required by applicable law. You can see when this Privacy Policy was last updated by checking the date at the top of this page. You are responsible for periodically reviewing this Privacy Policy. 

**Data Protection Management**  
SportsTG Pty Ltd  
Level 12, 565 Bourke Street  
MELBOURNE, VIC, 3000

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please send a detailed message to [privacy@sportstg.com](mailto:privacy@sportstg.com) or by mail to the address listed above.
